Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS.357
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 1976 - 1988
  - Pop Tarts at Danceteria, December 15, 1986; ID: 357.0043 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0043, Box 24, Dvd 357.0043)
  - The Sound of Muzak, April 21, 1986; ID: 357.0044 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0044, Box 24, Dvd 357.0044_pt.1, Dvd 357.0044_pt.2)
  - Sylvia Miles Screen Test, Brant's Music Video, undated; ID: 357.0045 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0045, Box 24, Dvd 357.0045)
  - Dinah Prince at Limelight, June 2, 1986; ID: 357.0046 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0046, Box 24, Dvd 357.0046)
  - Gaylord, Alexis, John Sex, Joey Arias at Limelight, February 2, 1986; ID: 357.0047 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0047, Box 24, Dvd 357.0047)
  - Cookie Watkins and Company at Cat Club, February 18, 1986; ID: 357.0048 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0048, Box 24, Dvd 357.0048)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger in Leer and Casanova at Performing Garage, March 8, 1986; ID: 357.0049 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0049, Box 24, Dvd 357.0049_pt.1, Dvd 357.0049_pt.2)
  - Follies at Cat Club, Walking Blackout (late night), Pyramid, March 13, 1986; ID: 357.0050 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0050, Box 24, Dvd 357.0050)
  - Cruel Story of Youth at The Dive, March 13, 1986; ID: 357.0051 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0051, Box 24, Dvd 357.0051)
  - Bowling with Eric Conrad, TishGervaise at Danceteria, February 1986; ID: 357.0052 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0052, Box 24, Dvd 357.0052)
    [1] -- Bowling with Eric Conrad, 2/14/1986 [2] -- TishGervaise at Danceteria, 2/22/1986
  - Gaga's going away in Manhattan Plaza (with Eric, Morgan, Elmer, Jimmie), May 7, 1986; ID: 357.0053 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0053, Box 24, Dvd 357.0053)
  - Michael Musto and John Sex at Palladium, John Sex at The Saint, 1986; ID: 357.0054 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0054, Box 24, Dvd 357.0054_pt.1, Dvd 357.0054_pt.2)
    [1] -- Michael Musto at Palladium [2] -- John Sex at Palladium, 3/28/1986 [3] -- John Sex at The Saint, 4/4/1986
  - Patricia Field's Hat Party at Area, October 28, 1985; ID: 357.0055 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0055, Box 24, Dvd 357.0055)
  - Now Explosion at Danceteria, January 26, 1985; ID: 357.0056 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0056, Box 24, Dvd 357.0056)
  - Albert Crudo at Danceteria, July 18, 1985; ID: 357.0057 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0057, Box 25, Dvd 357.0057)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, January 25, 1985; ID: 357.0058 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0058, Box 25, Dvd 357.0058)
  - 4th July with Rhonda and fireworks show on East River, July 4, 1983; ID: 357.0059 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0059, Box 25, Dvd 357.0059)
  - Holly Woodlawn's Park Avenue Party (tape #1), October 26, 1985; ID: 357.0060 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0060, Box 25, Dvd 357.0060)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger's Fowl Ball at Pyramid, November 9, 1985; ID: 357.0061 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0061, Box 25, Dvd 357.0061_pt.1, Dvd 357.0061_pt.2)
  - Pop Tarts with Bunny, Love Delegation at Cat Club, September 25, 1985; ID: 357.0062 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0062, Box 25, Dvd 357.0062)
  - Holly Woodlawn's Park Avenue Party #2, Bunny at Danceteria, October 26, 1985; ID: 357.0063 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0063, Box 25, Dvd 357.0063)
  - Emo Boutique Opening, November 19, 1985; ID: 357.0064 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0064, Box 25, Dvd 357.0064)
  - Alexis Jungle Gardenia at Cat Club, John Sex at Limelight, 1985-1986; ID: 357.0065 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0065, Box 25, Dvd 357.0065)
    [1] -- Alexis Jungle Gardenia at Cat Club, 10/21/1985 [2] -- John Sex at Limelight, 1/5/1986
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid (after the show), December 21, 1985; ID: 357.0066 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0066, Box 25, Dvd 357.0066)
    Includes: Pyramid dressing room, van, and Nightbirds.
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, December 21, 1985; ID: 357.0067 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0067, Box 25, Dvd 357.0067)
  - Pop Tarts, Dean Johnson at Limelight, November 17, 1985; ID: 357.0068 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0068, Box 25, Dvd 357.0068)
  - Holly Woodlawn's Birthday at Limelight, October 1, 1985; ID: 357.0069 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0069, Box 25, Dvd 357.0069)
  - Jill Lynne Opening, Mark-on-Hudson, November 11, 1985; ID: 357.0070 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0070, Box 25, Dvd 357.0070)
  - Fred R-M's Birthday at Caroline's, Vito's Awards at Limelight, 1985-1986; ID: 357.0071 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0071, Box 25, Dvd 357.0071)
    [1] -- Fred R-M's Birthday at Caroline's, 10/8/1985 [2] -- Vito's Awards at Limelight, 1/9/1986
  - Pyramid with Tanya Ransom, Kennon Raines, 3 Teens Kill 4, September 5, 1985; ID: 357.0072 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0072, Box 25, Dvd 357.0072)
  - Taboo at Pyramid, October 10, 1985; ID: 357.0073 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0073, Box 25, Dvd 357.0073)
  - Andy Anderson's Birthday at Tish's, October 12, 1985; ID: 357.0074 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0074, Box 25, Dvd 357.0074)
  - John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, October 20, 1985; ID: 357.0075 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0075, Box 25, Dvd 357.0075)
    Featuring: Billy Gallo, Mary K., Bobby S.
  - Tish's TV Star Search at Limelight, August 28, 1985; ID: 357.0076 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0076, Box 25, Dvd 357.0076)
    Currently unavailable.
  - New Music Seminar-Friday at Hotel with Now Explosion and Bunny, undated; ID: 357.0077 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0077, Box 25, Dvd 357.0077)
  - New Music Seminar-Saturday at Hotel, September 28, 1985; ID: 357.0078 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0078, Box 25, Dvd 357.0078)
  - New Music Seminar-Thursday at Hotel, September 26, 1985; ID: 357.0079 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0079, Box 25, Dvd 357.0079)
  - New Music Seminar-Saturday, Now Explosion at Pyramid, September 28, 1985; ID: 357.0080 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0080, Box 25, Dvd 357.0080)
  - New Music Seminar-Sunday, Pyramid with Rosie, Lizette, Lahoma, Larry Tee, and Bunny, September 29, 1985; ID: 357.0081 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0081, Box 25, Dvd 357.0081)
  - New Music Seminar-Friday with hurricane at Hotel, September 27, 1985; ID: 357.0082 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0082, Box 25, Dvd 357.0082)
  - Downtown Dukes with Sylvain Sylvain at Limelight, July 1, 1985; ID: 357.0083 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0083, Box 25, Dvd 357.0083)
  - Vito Bruno Boat Party, June 18, 1986; ID: 357.0084 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0084, Box 25, Dvd 357.0084)
  - Downtown Dukes II with Holly Woodlawn as emcee at Limelight, September 17, 1985; ID: 357.0085 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0085, Box 25, Dvd 357.0085)
    Cast List: Holly Woodlawn (emcee) 1) Michael Musto - I Want U Back 2) Hoy Boy 3) Pop Tarts 4) Dear Johns 5) Ned Sublette 6) John Collins 7) Zette 8) Randy Jones 9) Emanem [Johns] 10) [Sylva. Sylver] 11) Earl [Scoote] 12) David Johansen
  - Vito Bruno Downtown Awards at Limelight, Outlaw Party at Boat Basin, 1986; ID: 357.0086 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0086, Box 25, Dvd 357.0086)
    [1] -- Vito Bruno Downtown Awards at Limelight, 1/9/1986 [2] -- Outlaw Party at Boat Basin, 5/15/1986
  - Vito Bruno's Outlaw Parties, 1985; ID: 357.0087 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0087, Box 25, Dvd 357.0087)
    [1] -- Outlaw Party/Williamsburg Bridge, 6/6/1985 [2] -- Halloween, 1985
  - Boston, Whales in Boston, 1985; ID: 357.0088 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0088, Box 25, Dvd 357.0088)
    [1] -- Boston, 7/7/1985 [2] -- Whales in Boston, 7/11/1985
  - Andy Warhol at Fiorucci, February 14, 1986; ID: 357.0090 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0090, Box 25, Dvd 357.0090)
  - Duet or Die at Limelight, November 26, 1985; ID: 357.0091 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0091, Box 25, Dvd 357.0091)
  - Gabriel Rotello's Downtown Divas and Dukes at Limelight, January 13, 1986; ID: 357.0092 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0092, Box 25, Dvd 357.0092)
  - Wendy Wild at Cat Club, August 1985; ID: 357.0094 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0094, Box 25, Dvd 357.0094)
    [1] -- Wendy Wilde at Cat Club, 8/5/1985 [2] -- Bansi Strip Death at Cat Club, 8/5/1985 [3] -- W.W. + Mad Violets at Pyramid, 8/8/1985
  - Brant and Rhonda's Wedding, November 8, 1985; ID: 357.0095 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0095, Box 26, Dvd 357.0095)
  - RuPaul Walk, July 28, 1984; ID: 357.0096 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0096, Box 26, Dvd 357.0096)
  - Peter Pan at Danceteria, December 12, 1983; ID: 357.0098 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0098, Box 26, Dvd 357.0098)
  - Downtown Dukes and Divas First Anniversary, February 9, 1986; ID: 357.0099 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0099, Box 26, Dvd 357.0099)
  - RuPaul Mix, July 10, 1986; ID: 357.0100 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0100, Box 26, Dvd 357.0100)
    RuPaul is Starbooty Video Album, Terror I, Terror II, Terror 3-D, Star Booty The Movie, and much more
  - Mama Said Brunch, undated; ID: 357.0101 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0101, Box 26, Dvd 357.0101)
  - Mama Said Beauty Show #1 Original, undated; ID: 357.0125 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0125, Box 26, Dvd 357.0125)
  - Mama Said Beauty Show #2 Original, undated; ID: 357.0124 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0124, Box 26, Dvd 357.0124)
  - Mama Said Beauty Shop Sequences #3, undated; ID: 357.0093 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0093, Box 26, Dvd 357.0093)
  - Mama Said Inserts, undated; ID: 357.0109 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0109, Box 26, Dvd 357.0109)
  - Mama Said Florida Inserts, undated; ID: 357.0130 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0130, Box 26, Dvd 357.0130)
  - Mama Said Unedited, undated; ID: 357.0111 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0111, Box 26, Dvd 357.0111)
  - Mama Said Copy of Original, undated; ID: 357.0126 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0126, Box 26, Dvd 357.0126)
  - Mama Said Music - Baby Kelly Sings, undated; ID: 357.0121 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0121, Box 26, Dvd 357.0121)
  - Madonna Impersonators at Pyramid, July 26, 1985; ID: 357.0102 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0102, Box 26, Dvd 357.0102)
  - Christina at Danceteria, February 1, 1986; ID: 357.0103 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0103, Box 26, Dvd 357.0103)
  - Liz and Albert Roof Party, undated; ID: 357.0104 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0104, Box 26, Dvd 357.0104)
  - Alexis Del Lago's Jungle Gardenia and Road Furrier (with Hapi Phace & Philly) at Pyramid, August 4, 1985; ID: 357.0105 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0105, Box 26, Dvd 357.0105)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, August 11, 1985; ID: 357.0106 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0106, Box 26, Dvd 357.0106_pt.1, Dvd 357.0106_pt.2)
    Sunday with Hapi, Loretta, Rosie, Bunny, Ethyl, Kennon, Wendy, etc.
  - Noh versus Musto - Trivial Pursuit on Nelson's Roof, August 3, 1985; ID: 357.0107 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0107, Box 26, Dvd 357.0107)
  - Halloween 1985, October 31, 1985; ID: 357.0108 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0108, Box 26, Dvd 357.0108)
    Features: Parade, Vito's, Water C., and Pyramid
  - Vito Bruno Party Mix of Events, undated; ID: 357.0110 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0110, Box 26, Dvd 357.0110)
    O-Party Mix 2425 - Now Explosion 2710 - John Sex 2900 - Now Explosion 3050 - RuPaul 3215 - Cocktail Girls 3340 - Bunny Chase 3620 - Kilpig 3980 - Cookie Watkins 4188 - Shazork 4380 - Mr. Fashion 4560 - Now Explosion 4800 - RuPaul 4960 - Now Explosion 5140 - Now Explosion 5250 - Times Square
  - Vito Bruno's Glamour + Gossip, Pizza a Go Go, August 1, 1984; ID: 357.0112 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0112, Box 26, Dvd 357.0112)
  - Vito Bruno's Musto at Pizza a Go Go with Street the Beat, October 10, 1984; ID: 357.0113 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0113, Box 26, Dvd 357.0113)
  - Downtown Divas III at Limelight, August 12, 1985; ID: 357.0114 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0114, Box 26, Dvd 357.0114)
    Featuring: Debbie Cole, Lisa [Koutoukos], Kristie Rose, Holly Woodlawn, [Tish] + Smoky, Cookie Watkins, Ula Hedwig, Cherry Vanilla
  - Jennifer's East Village Wedding, July 28, 1985; ID: 357.0115 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0115, Box 26, Dvd 357.0115)
  - City Harvest Benefit, October 16, 1985; ID: 357.0116 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0116, Box 26, Dvd 357.0116)
  - Surf's Up Studio 54, July 30, 1985; ID: 357.0117 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0117, Box 26, Dvd 357.0117)
  - Halloween Dukes and Divas at Limelight, October 29, 1985; ID: 357.0118 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0118, Box 26, Dvd 357.0118)
  - John Sex at Cat Club, Talk Show at Musto's, July 29, 1985; ID: 357.0119 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0119, Box 26, Dvd 357.0119)
  - The Gong Show at Limelight, September 19, 1985; ID: 357.0120 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0120, Box 26, Dvd 357.0120)
  - The Must at Limelight, September 10, 1985; ID: 357.0122 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0122, Box 26, Dvd 357.0122)
  - The Clowns Rambozo at Pyramid, September 15, 1985; ID: 357.0123 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0123, Box 26, Dvd 357.0123)
    Featuring: Allen, Happi, Philly, Tabboo, Sally Randall, John Sex, Dean Johnson, Pat Orozco, Brian Trey
  - Glamour + Gossip - Vito Bruno at Pizza a Go Go, August 7, 1985; ID: 357.0127 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0127, Box 26, Dvd 357.0127)
  - VHS Dubs, undated; ID: 357.0128 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0128, Box 26, Dvd 357.0128)
  - Hamlette with Ethel Eichelberger, February 9, 1985; ID: 357.0129 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0129, Box 26, Dvd 357.0129)
  - Mix Tape: Copy of Joey Arias and Copy of Vito Mix, October 2, 1986; ID: 357.0131 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0131, Box 26, Dvd 357.0131)
  - Miami Vice with Sylvia Miles as Guest Star, undated; ID: 357.0132 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0132, Box 26, Dvd 357.0132)
  - Blackout Takes a Walk; Blackout's Birthday Surprise; Nelson Home Movie, undated; ID: 357.0133 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0133, Box 26, Dvd 357.0133)
  - Eddie on Wall Street (Original Edit Copy), undated; ID: 357.0134 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0134, Box 26, Dvd 357.0134_pt.1, Dvd 357.0134_pt.2)
  - Bunny Chase Original, June 26, 1985; ID: 357.0135 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0135, Box 26, Dvd 357.0135)
  - Kristie Rose at Limelight, October 16, 1985; ID: 357.0136 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0136, Box 26, Dvd 357.0136)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, July 28, 1984; ID: 357.0137 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0137, Box 26, Dvd 357.0137)
  - Alice in Boston, September 5, 1984; ID: 357.0138 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0138, Box 26, Dvd 357.0138)
  - Family Outing, March 27, 1985; ID: 357.0139 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0139, Box 26, Dvd 357.0139)
    Featuring: Albert, Rhonda, Nathan, and Summer
  - Cocktail Girlz at Pyramid, October 11, 1985; ID: 357.0140 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0140, Box 27, Dvd 357.0140)
  - Glamour + Gossip with Beauregard Houston-Montgomery and Oliver at Pizza a Go Go, August 1, 1984; ID: 357.0141 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0141, Box 27, Dvd 357.0141)
  - Sylvia Miles in Oh Dad, Poor Dad in Provincetown, August 25, 1984; ID: 357.0142 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0142, Box 27, Dvd 357.0142)
  - Miss Margie at Lucky 7, February 26, 1985; ID: 357.0143 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0143, Box 27, Dvd 357.0143)
  - Friday with Sylvia and Alice in Provincetwon, 1984; ID: 357.0144 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0144, Box 27, Dvd 357.0144)
  - Saturday with Sylvia in Provincetown, 1984; ID: 357.0145 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0145, Box 27, Dvd 357.0145)
  - Chip Duckett For Florida Only, 1989; ID: 357.0146 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0146, Box 27, Dvd 357.0146)
  - Dean Johnson at Pyramid, September 21, 1985; ID: 357.0147 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0147, Box 27, Dvd 357.0147)
  - The Ritz, February 14, 1985; ID: 357.0148 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0148, Box 27, Dvd 357.0148_pt.1, Dvd 357.0148_pt.2)
  - Gaga's Birthday, July 24, 1984; ID: 357.0150 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0150)
  - L + K Man - Original Edit Madame Rosa's, September 6, 1986; ID: 357.0151 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0151, Box 27, Dvd 357.0151)
  - Mama Said Artists, Pyramid Float, undated; ID: 357.0152 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0152, Box 27, Dvd 357.0152)
  - Gay Pride March, 1983; ID: 357.0153 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0153, Box 27, Dvd 357.0153)
  - Sylvia Miles - Sunday Night Closing of Play in Provincetown, 1984; ID: 357.0154 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0154, Box 27, Dvd 357.0154)
  - James Dean Tribute at Limelight, September 24, 1985; ID: 357.0155 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0155, Box 27, Dvd 357.0155)
    Featuring: Cherry Vanilla, Lina Koutrakos, Earl Scooter, and Cookie Watkins
  - Studio 54, October 9, 1984; ID: 357.0156 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0156, Box 27, Dvd 357.0156)
  - Glamour + Gossip, Pizza a Go Go, August 7, 1985; ID: 357.0157 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0157, Box 27, Dvd 357.0157)
  - The Saint Japan Fashion Show, January 16, 1986; ID: 357.0158 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0158, Box 27, Dvd 357.0158)
    Copy of edit #1
  - Blackout Takes a Walk, Blackout's Birthday Surprise, undated; ID: 357.0159 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0159, Box 27, Dvd 357.0159)
  - Scene Queens at Palladium, April 24, 1986; ID: 357.0160 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0160, Box 27, Dvd 357.0160)
  - Mahogony at Pyramid, May 3, 1984; ID: 357.0163 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0163, Box 27, Dvd 357.0163)
  - Mewborns in New York, June 24, 1984; ID: 357.0164 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0164, Box 27, Dvd 357.0164)
  - Sylvia Miles in Provincetown, August 25, 1984; ID: 357.0165 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0165, Box 27, Dvd 357.0165)
  - Now Explosion with Kennon at Pyramid, June 23, 1985; ID: 357.0166 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0166, Box 27, Dvd 357.0166)
    Featuring: Dick, Alan Mace, Brian, Isadora, and Angelo
  - Palladium to Nightbirds, May 15, 1985; ID: 357.0167 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0167, Box 27, Dvd 357.0167_pt.1, Dvd 357.0167_pt.2)
    Featuring: Albert, Musto, Tish, Sandy D., Eric, and Bill L.
  - Pat Field Copy of Edit, undated; ID: 357.0168 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0168, Box 27, Dvd 357.0168)
  - Uptown Dukes and Divas at Limelight, April 27, 1986; ID: 357.0169 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0169, Box 27, Dvd 357.0169)
  - Morning Walk with Blackout, Pyramid Dubs for Clayton, undated; ID: 357.0170 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0170, Box 27, Dvd 357.0170)
  - Cookie Watkins at Kenny's Castaway, January 1, 1986; ID: 357.0171 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0171, Box 27, Dvd 357.0171)
  - Gaylord's 1939 World's Fair and Limelight, May 4, 1986; ID: 357.0172 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0172, Box 27, Dvd 357.0172)
  - RuPaul at Pyramid, July 27, 1984; ID: 357.0173 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0173, Box 27, Dvd 357.0173)
  - Sylvia Miles in Oh Dad, Poor Dad in River Arts, Woodstock, July 29, 1984; ID: 357.0174 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0174, Box 27, Dvd 357.0174)
  - Atlanta #2, August 17, 1983; ID: 357.0175 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0175, Box 27, Dvd 357.0175)
  - Zette at Limelight, April 28, 1986; ID: 357.0176 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0176, Box 27, Dvd 357.0176)
  - Alice: Boston to New York, July 12, 1985; ID: 357.0177 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0177, Box 27, Dvd 357.0177)
  - Sunny Bak at Latin Quarter, August 26, 1985; ID: 357.0178 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0178, Box 28, Dvd 357.0178_pt.1, Dvd 357.0178_pt.2)
  - Road trip to Atlanta with Dick Kershaw, December 22, 1984; ID: 357.0179 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0179, Box 28, Dvd 357.0179)
  - The Musto Miracle, Easter, 1985; ID: 357.0180 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0180, Box 28, Dvd 357.0180)
  - Gilligan's Pyramid, August 24, 1985; ID: 357.0181 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0181, Box 28, Dvd 357.0181)
  - Kennon and Adam Purple at Garden of Eden, Hiro, 7-A, August 11, 1985; ID: 357.0182 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0182, Box 28, Dvd 357.0182)
  - Downtown Divas II at Limelight, May 16, 1985; ID: 357.0183 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0183, Box 28, Dvd 357.0183)
  - Atlanta and Kershaw Christmas, 1984; ID: 357.0184 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0184, Box 28, Dvd 357.0184)
  - Mary Kaye and Bobby's Party, May 1983; ID: 357.0185 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0185, Box 28, Dvd 357.0185)
  - Bunny Hop at Studio 54, April 20, 1984; ID: 357.0186 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0186, Box 28, Dvd 357.0186)
  - Jamie Deroy Greene Street, February 7, 1985; ID: 357.0187 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0187, Box 28, Dvd 357.0187)
  - Now Explosion at Danceteria, November 18, 1983; ID: 357.0188 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0188, Box 28, Dvd 357.0188)
  - Statue of Liberty with Toyo, undated; ID: 357.0189 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0189, Box 28, Dvd 357.0189)
  - The Musto Miracle Easter, 1985; ID: 357.0190 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0190, Box 28, Dvd 357.0190)
    This item has not been transferred and is not available to researchers. It is a duplicate of Media ID 357.0180.
  - Dean Johnson at The World, May 6, 1986; ID: 357.0191 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0191, Box 28, Dvd 357.0191)
  - Vito's Bridge Party for Annie Flanders, June 6, 1985; ID: 357.0192 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0192, Box 28, Dvd 357.0192)
  - AIDS Benefit, undated; ID: 357.0193 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0193, Box 28, Dvd 357.0193)
  - Provincetown, 1985; ID: 357.0194 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0194, Box 28, Dvd 357.0194)
  - Tish's "It's My Party", January 11, 1985; ID: 357.0195 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0195, Box 28, Dvd 357.0195)
  - Zora and Bill's Wedding #2, June 9, 1985; ID: 357.0197 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0197, Box 28, Dvd 357.0197)
  - Zora and Bill's Wedding #1, June 9, 1985; ID: 357.0198 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0198, Box 28, Dvd 357.0198)
  - Artwalk, October 18, 1984; ID: 357.0199 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0199, Box 28, Dvd 357.0199)
  - Tish and The Pop Tarts at Danceteria, July 26, 1985; ID: 357.0200 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0200, Box 28, Dvd 357.0200)
  - Philly and Richard Hoffman - Historica Pagentia Fashionista Absurdia at Pyramid, August 10, 1985; ID: 357.0201 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0201, Box 28, Dvd 357.0201)
  - Now Explosion with Kennon and Her Snake, June 23, 1985; ID: 357.0202 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0202, Box 28, Dvd 357.0202)
  - Now Explosion Big Pussy Show at Pyramid, June 21, 1985; ID: 357.0203 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0203, Box 28, Dvd 357.0203)
  - Halloween, October 31, 1984; ID: 357.0204 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0204, Box 28, Dvd 357.0204)
  - Kershaw, June 1985; ID: 357.0205 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0205, Box 28, Dvd 357.0205)
    [1] -- Kershaw, 6/28/1985 [2] -- Kershaw, 6/29/1985
  - La Dolce Micahel Musto Party at Danceteria, December 12, 1984; ID: 357.0206 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0206, Box 28, Dvd 357.0206_pt.1, Dvd 357.0206_pt.2)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Dance Teen, April 18, 1985; ID: 357.0207 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0207, Box 28, Dvd 357.0207)
  - Alexis Del Lago's Garden Party, June 21, 1985; ID: 357.0208 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0208, Box 28, Dvd 357.0208)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger's Leer at 8BC, July 27, 1985; ID: 357.0209 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0209, Box 28, Dvd 357.0209)
  - Scott Wittman and Marc Shaiman's Nude Faces of 1985 at Danceteria, May 15, 1985; ID: 357.0210 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0210, Box 28, Dvd 357.0210)
  - Kennon, Voltaire, + Kristy Rose at Pyramid during New Music Seminar, September 26, 1985; ID: 357.0211 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0211, Box 28, Dvd 357.0211)
  - Hamlette with Ethel Eichelberger (first take), September 9, 1985; ID: 357.0212 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0212, Box 28, Dvd 357.0212_pt.1, Dvd 357.0212_pt.2)
  - Miss Margie and Lise, February 24, 1985; ID: 357.0213 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0213, Box 28, Dvd 357.0213)
  - Vito's Bridge Party for Annie Flanders, June 6, 1985; ID: 357.0214 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0214, Box 28, Dvd 357.0214)
  - Tish's "It's My Party, Again" at Limelight, August 21, 1985; ID: 357.0215 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0215, Box 28, Dvd 357.0215)
  - Sylvia in Woodstock, July 29, 1985; ID: 357.0216 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0216, Box 29, Dvd 357.0216)
  - Nelson's Film School Movies, 1972-1976; ID: 357.0217 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0217, Box 29, Dvd 357.0217_pt.1, Dvd 357.0217_pt.2)
    Nelson's Film School Movies: Fire Island 1976, Inside Disco, Walk Around Manhattan, Good Motim Montage, Sunshine in NY 1972 with Douglas and Chou and Blackout takes a walk in stop motion, Ride on Subway, Picture of Nelson, Nelson Tour of Mannequins at [Gimblls] 1972, Central Park, The Piers, Gay Bedroom Scene, Things to Look At, Movements
  - Now Explosion on MTV, undated; ID: 357.0218 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0218)
  - Mahogony at Pyramid, May 3, 1984; ID: 357.0219 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0219, Box 29, Dvd 357.0219)
  - Axelrod Wedding Party, October 27, 1984; ID: 357.0220 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0220, Box 29, Dvd 357.0220)
  - La Dolce Musto Party at Danceteria (Copy), 1984; ID: 357.0221 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0221, Box 29, Dvd 357.0221)
    This item has not been transferred and is not available to researchers. It is a duplicate of Media ID 357.0206.
  - Brant Mewborn "A Love That Lasts Forever" Original and NBC Dub, undated; ID: 357.0222 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0222)
  - Sylvia Miles on Joe Franklin, July 13, 1984; ID: 357.0223 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0223)
  - Downtown Divas at Limelight, April 9, 1985; ID: 357.0224 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0224, Box 29, Dvd 357.0224)
  - Nude Faces at Danceteria, 1985; ID: 357.0225 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0225, Box 29, Dvd 357.0225)